McIntosh Stereopticon Company
Marist Archives and Special Collections
McIntosh Stereopticon Company
2.1.2.4.24
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1410
- McIntosh Stereopticon Company, 2.1.2.4.24
  - The Great Statue of Christopher Columbus, Genoa, Italy, circa 1900-1915; 28; 178; 3x4 color (Box 1410)
  - Castle San Angelo and bridge, Rome Italy, circa 1900-1915; 29; 220; 3x4 color (Box 1410)
  - Basilica of Constantine, Rome, Italy, circa 1900-1915; 30; 351; 3x4 color (Box 1410)
  - The Wrestlers, Uffizi Gallery, Florence, Italy, circa 1900-1915; 31; 389; 3x4 b&w (Box 1410)
  - Gallery, The Campo Santo, Genoa, Italy, circa 1900-1915; 32; 438; 3x4 b&w (Box 1410)
  - The Colosseum, Rome, Italy, circa 1900-1915; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1410)
  - Sarcophagus of Napoleon Bonaparte, Hotel des Invalides, Paris, Franc, circa 1900-1915; 34; 2514; 3x4 color (Box 1410)
  - Hotel des Invalides, Paris, France, circa 1900-1915; 35; 17497; 3x4 color (Box 1410)
  - Sunset on the Seine, Paris, France, circa 1900-1915; 36; 20851; 3x4 color (Box 1410)
  - The Madeleine Church, interior, Paris, France, circa 1900-1915; 37; 3x4 color (Box 1410)
  Box 1411
- McIntosh Stereopticon Company, 2.1.2.4.24
  - Palais Royale, Paris, France, circa 1900-1915; 1; 3x4 color (Box 1411)
  - Court of Farewell, Palace of Fontainebleau, France, circa 1900-1915; 2; 3x4 color (Box 1411)
  - Map of Panama and Costa Rica, circa 1900-1915; 3; 3x4 color (Box 1411)
  - Portals of the Gateway, Garden of the Gods, Colorado, circa 1900-1915; 4; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1411)
  - George Washington’s barn, Mount Vernon, Virginia, circa 1900-1915; 5; 132; 3x4 color (Box 1411)
  - A gorgeous sunset, circa 1900-1915; 6; 3x4 color (Box 1411)